krify.com 2013-10-05

# Web Development | Mobile Development Company | Krify Privacy

Krify Innovations (UK) Limited (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.  
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Krify Innovations (UK) Limited, registered under company number 08039809 with its registered office at Euro House, 1394 High Road, London, United Kingdom, N20 9YZ.  
**Information we may collect from you**  
We may collect and process the following data about you:  
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.krify.co.uk. This includes information provided at the time of completing the “Contact Us” form on our site, registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by Krify and when you report a problem with our site. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. Details of your visits to our site (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data) and the resources that you access.

**IP addresses**  
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.  
**Cookies**  
For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on your browser. Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. We only use “session cookies” which are deleted at the end of your browsing session for the purpose of authenticating any login or password details provided by you to access parts of our site. We do not use any cookies that contain information that is transferred to or stored the hard drive of your computer. If you register with us or if you continue to use our site, you agree to our use of cookies.  
Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Uses made of the information**  
We use information held about you in the following ways:  
To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.  
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.  
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.  
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.  
To notify you about changes to our service.  
We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by email, post or telephone.  
If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the “Contact Us” form).  
We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

**Disclosure of your information**  
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.  
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:  
If we enter into a promotional, advertising or supply arrangement with third parties , in which case we may disclose your personal data to those third parties for marketing purposes or to follow up on any enquiry made by you through the Website.  
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.  
If Krify Innovations (UK) Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers and enquirers will be one of the transferred assets.  
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use our terms of use

and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Krify, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Your rights**  
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at privacy@krify.net.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.  
Access to information  
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.  
Changes to our privacy policy  
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.  
**Contact**  
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to privacy@krify.net
